1. Annyeonghaseyo. Nayoosujongri Damdangjaibnida.
2. Daegawisihanhan Kodonghagyoesiyokungiyokjoginilibiyoleojiyoseyoyo.
3. Hwagindoyoyahalsasiliyun. Namnyeyogyosagabujyojiyolanhayengdongyolhayestanyunminwayonjegiyedayhangiyosebnida.
4. Tugihangiyon. Iryolilbuhaksayengijijyobmogyokhayestanyeunjiyomibnida.
5. Sejyoniteyojinduigyoyoksiyongiyonidugyoseyodeheyjugakjigwehayejeyjosiriyolhesiyoyo.
6. Idiyolgyosanyunjasenduliyohengdongyodayehaye. Buinhagoizdagohabnida.
7. Gyeolgwanyunajigmijyongijiman. Gyeogyolgwaryolgidarinyungwajyongunbunmyonghigorulgyosebnida.
8. Majimaguro. Gyeodeupgangjohajiman. Idugyosaidaeyahanjonghwakhansasilhwaginipilyohabnida.
9. Wonyulienyusujongri. Yeogigajibnida.
10. Dayeumsiganedo myonghwakhanniyusujongburokajabweobyesseobnida.