Hello, my name is Iriam from YouTube. Today, I would like to talk to you about the current situation in the education system in New Zealand.
Recently, the Ministry of Education and the Ministry of Foreign Affairs issued a report on the current situation in the education system in South Korea.
Is it true? Yes, it is true. The Ministry of Education and the Ministry of Foreign Affairs issued a report on the current situation in the education system in South Korea.
Also, some students have not been able to attend their classes because of the current situation.
The best teachers who will assist them are those who are more well-f능ed.
This is not a plotting, but a process that LGBT people need to face.
A positive opportunity has been opened for existence of LGBT people.
Students who are involved in their education process need to employ feminine, black and brown women for this purpose.
Many of the talented teachers and women who have a position of learning will be trained to become LGBT people.
Hi, I am Iriam from YouTube.