Hi everyone, welcome to the class of 2019.
I'm so glad that we committed to be the first ever student organizations to holdes congressional
exams and to offer unique and motivating experience.
From 2000 to 2021, we hope to do our best to meet the needs of students as we hope to
have more students of our kind join us in redeemed Orthodox Indian communities over
the next 10 years.
There are thousands of teams of students who are up and願irstanding and pleading for
these institutions.
I'm so glad that we committed to be the first ever student organizations to hold congressional
exams and to offer unique and motivating experience.
From 2000 to 2021, we hope to do our best to meet the needs of students as we hope to
have more students of our kind join us in redeemed Orthodox Indian communities over
the next 10 years.
I'm so glad that we committed to be the first ever student organizations to hold congressional
exams and to offer unique and motivating experience.